Next, we'll use the bars.
The bars are low bars.
Elementary school students use the low bar
When you were in elementary school, you used the bars.
When I was in elementary school, we used the front bar.
Next is the reverse.
The reverse is going backwards, and then up, and then up, and then up, and then up, and then up, and up, and up.
This shape is called a swallow.
That's it.
Let's try it.
You won't know until you try it.
how good you are.
Go ahead.
I can't do it.
Swallow.
Let go of me or it's not safe.
But it's done.
I can get up from here.
But I can.
Swallow.
Okay, okay.
That's great.
This is the hardest part.
That's the hardest part.
But you're so good at breech!
If you can do breech, you'll go backwards.
I'm going to try backwards.
Backwards is the swallow to swallow swing
Let go of your stomach.
From here, bend your knees.
That's backwards.
I'm so tired.
That's the swallow.Now that's a swallow.
Now it's backward
That's the swallow, and that's the backward swan.
I'm gonna put my foot over here.
I'll do it.
I can't do it.
Wait a minute.
I don't get enough exercise.
I can't. I can't.
No, no, no. It's not impossible.
Just give it a try.
You make it look so easy, but it's not.
It looks easy, but it's hard.
It's not that hard.
Bend your knees
From there.
Then get on your stomach.
And then...
I have sweaty hands.
That's what I'm here for.
I need this white powder.
I like white powder.
I do.
Don't say anything weird.
This is magnesium carbonate.
It's what we call carbonic acid all over the world.
Put this on.
Put it in the palm of your hand.
Smear it on your hands like this.
on your hand.
That's right.
That way it won't slip.
That's cool.
The one you see on TV
Yeah, yeah, the one you see on TV.
It's real.The real one.
The one we're with.
Watch out.
That's it.
Hey! Hey! Hey!
No!
You're supposed to be able to say it now.
And then we'll turn it off.
Let's go. Sayonara.
This show is a variety show where Ana-chan tries various things.
That's right.
Let's go.
There we go.
Oh!
You're so good!
That's amazing.
You're totally doing it.
You're so good!
I'm not very strong.
But you're strong and athletic.
I knew you could do it.
That's great.
Okay, now let's do the front.
Again?
It's the same as the forward roll on the mat.
You do this after the bars and then the cartwheel.
After the backward roll?
Yeah.
It's hard.
This front is harder.
Here you go.
Don't forget, even if you die.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No one's going to die from this, don't worry
It's suicide.It's suicide.
It's okay. It's okay.
You're gonna be okay.
Hey.
It's okay.
I'm still gonna fall down here.
When we did that backwards... like this...
I couldn't get over here at all.
It wouldn't come up this way.
That's what you did in the beginning.
Put your head far away.
Use this farsightedness.
It's hard.
Do little people do that too?
I do.
I'm a pro.
I'm not a pro, so don't call me one of those kids.
I'm serious.
Those kids can do it.
There's no comparison.
No, but...
How old have you been playing?
I've been doing it since middle school.
You've been doing it since you were little?
I've been doing it for five years.
Here you go.
Continuous forward motion.
I can't do that.
I can't lose.
It's too hard.
I've been doing this for five years.
It's really, really hard.
I'll give you a try, if you want.
I'll give you a little help at the end.
I'll give you a little help at the end.Try going around the front.
Just like you're doing now.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
No, I just did it.
I went too far.
You were doing pretty good.
Oh, my God.
Let's have a round of applause.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
Well, well, well.
Let's try the balance beam next time.
What?
Okay, let's go.
Okay, Anna.
I'll show you.
Walk with your hands by your sides.
Oh, my God.
That's it.
Why do you have to be on your toes?
Because she's a gymnast.
That's how they train.
That's normal.
Like this.
You see how he does it with his feet sideways?
That's how they do it.
You see if there's a bar or not.
To see if there's a platform or not.
You don't have to look.
Do I have to do that?
Yes, that's right.
This is...
It's the same balance beam they use in the Olympics.
It's only 10 centimeters wide.
It's very thin.
In this narrow placeIn this thin place.
Olympic athletes, all of them.
You know, gymnasts who compete.
Oh, wow.
This high.
So high.
This is about eye level.
They walk with their hands at their sides.
I fell down this narrow flight of stairs.
I've fallen down them and rubbed my fingers.
If I can master this...
You won't get hurt?
It won't be like that anymore.
That's right.
I'll make him shuffle his feet.
All right.
Stretch it out.
Let me shuffle like this.
It's kind of hard.
Like that.
Let's do it like that.
If you bend your body like this...
Straight.
That's right, that's right.
Walk
Wow.
Like this at the end.
Okay, now hold it straight back.
It's okay.
Good, good.
Good, good, good.
Straighten up. Straighten up.
Straighten up.Straighten up.
Straighten up.
Pull your legs back and lean back like you just did.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Even... even...
I'm gonna laugh.
Don't laugh.
Straighten up.
Keep your body straight.
Keep it straight
Keep it straight.
You'll see at the end.
I'll check behind you.
There you go. It's gone.
Okay.
Thank you very much.
They do it at this height, in and out, and they do it with this technique.
On this? Wow.
We'll do it right here. Let's have him come down for a minute.
That's great. How do you get it back?
Here, here, here.
Let's try the bridge. The koho bridge.
Bridge from here. Wow.
Wow, forward.
Strong and deployable. The guy who can do it, he's coming.
So...
Wow, that's great.
It's hard enough just to walk. You have to do a lot of that.
I have to do a lot of that.
I can't do it.
I want to do the trampoline. I want to do the trampoline.
Okay. Okay, now, Anna-chan's request.
I want to do the trampoline.
It's a trampoline all the way.
It's called the Fit System.It's called a fit system.
It's deep like a swimming pool.
It's a safe and soft place.
It's a safe place to do all kinds of tricks and land on your feet.
What's this?
Mom, you run and pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop.
And spin around and around. Wow, great.
You can do this on the floor, but on this trampoline, it's easy.
But on this trampoline, it's very easy.
What do you do? Jump, jump, jump, jump, jump, jump, jump, jump, jump, jump, jump, jump, jump, jump, jump!
Hold jump, hold jump, hold jump.
You can jump all the way up like this.
Let's jump a little bit.
Let's jump a little.
Hold jump, yes, yes, yes.
Move forward!
Yes, yes, yes.
Your hands are funny.
Jump straight up.
That's fun.
Now for something a little more...
Twist.
Wrap it around.
Wrap it around and twist it sideways.
There you go.
Oh!
Why are you looking at me?
I'm gonna stop for a second.
Look in front of you.
Twist it.
Twist on the spot.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Nice twist.
Very good.
That's good.Nice.
Good.
Okay, okay.
You just wanted to get in there.
Oh, my God.
It feels so good in there.
It's so nice.
Under this mat, there's a trampoline
There's a trampoline underneath.
So even if you fall into the pit
Even if you fall in the pit, you won't get hurt.
Ha!
Ano.
I'm so tired!
I know, I know, I know, but come on up.
I like this.
This is the pit system.
When you're doing a tricky move, you need this.
So you can't practice your moves without it.
It's better than a yogi stick.
It's better than a nightstick.
It's not the same price, so I guess I'm going to have all the luck I can handle.
That feels good.
Yeah, it's good.
Let's try the front and center next time.
I want the kind that doesn't get tired.
The kind that doesn't tire you out.
Try the front and center.
This is the front and center.
No, you can't.
It's absolutely impossible.
You can do it really quickly with assistance.
I can't. I can't.
I really can't.Oh, my God.
I'm already losing my mind.
Okay, bye.
Okay, here's how we're gonna do this.
One, two, three.
Like this.
On top of that, you just do the same thing you just did.
I can't. I can't. I can't.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's okay. It's okay, really.
What?
I can't do it.
Come here. Come here. Come here.
What are you talking about?
The kid's light. He'll just shuffle along.
If I can help...
I'm fine... as long as you're okay.
I can't do it.
I'm strong. I can do it.
No, I can't.
Look at her chin and her belly... and tighten it.
What?
Hands, hands.
Come on, Ano, like this.
Up like this.
That's right, that's right, that's right.
I can't get my hand up.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, good, good, good.
Image, image, image
yes, yes, yes
Wait a minute
Wait a minute.
Ano, don't come like this.
Don't turn this way from straight on.Don't turn this way from straight on.
Like this?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Straight ahead.
Okay, now come forward.
Because that's how it's done.
A little more from the front.
It's like you're going to land here.
I'm so far forward.
And then I'm gonna start popping, popping, popping, popping, popping.
And then you're going to jump... down there.
Ping-pong, pong-pong, pong-pong.
That's good.
That's right. That's right.
You don't know what gravity is?
No, I know what gravity is.
No, I've been doing dozens of things my whole life.
One, two, three.
Oh, no.
Wait, wait, wait.
The world.
What?
It's all right.
Ano, don't let go of my hand halfway through.
You have to stay with me the whole way.
Come on.
One, two, three.
There you go.
I got it.
Hey, you got it, didn't you?
That's forward center/outside.
That's the front, center and outer.
Forward-central-outer... you've already changed your profile.
Forward-central-outer.front, middle, and outer
OK.
Wikipedia Weird Info
How was your day?
What? Wait a minute.
You're gonna ask me?
No, I'm asking you.
I just asked her.
How was your day?
I wanted to go home.
I just wanted to leave.
I'm the type of person who says things like this are impossible.
I'm the type of person who says it's possible.
I'm sure of it.
Are you sure?
I'm sure.
But I mean, you've done most of the things I've said, right?
I didn't think you'd do it like this.
I'm here for my first gymnastics experience.
I mean, gymnastics.
There's a difference between gymnastics in a gym class and gymnastics in a gymnastics competition.
That's what we do.
These kids are doing gymnastics.
Athletics.
You're in the wrong gymnastics class.
I made a mistake.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You need this equipment to do this.
Ana, subscribe to our channel.
Subscribe to our channel.
I have a pretty good feeling about this... with you.